[Music] I'm so tired,
Oh my,
what's up, we've already made coffee at our house,
you still haven't eaten,
sister,
take the plate and put it away, let's wash it quickly,
oh why don't you go somewhere else,
he's getting hungry, go to him and slap him, you're going to slap him, you're going to slap him, you're going to slap him, you're going to slap him, you're going to slap him, you're going to slap him, baby,
tell me, is your brain
hot and your nose bleeding,
what's wrong, you're talking, you're talking, you're talking,
[music], have you
come, what's
wrong, Saravana, brother, has he come,
uncle, did your
son-in-law kiss you, did your mother kiss you, did your son-in-law kiss you, mummy, did your son-in-law kiss you, mummy, did your son-in-law kiss you, mummy, did your son-in-law kiss you, mummy, what's the water, where's the water, where's the water, oh my, did you go to the
temple where the water is poured in the morning, did you go
there, is there a water or
not, I'll come back on my
bike,
how many times will you come, baby?
[Music] What's that, you go
ahead and go ahead.
[Music]
There's coriander in my water, so there's a lot of
tulsi.
Overcrowded at the Perumal temple.
They put coriander in it because the basil was burnt.
That's what he says, kid.
What have you been doing?
Lord.
Oh, where can I go to tell this injustice?
Hey, why are you talking about a normal thing?
What is a normal thing?
What is the answer to the prayer in the temple? It's not like that.
From a young age, you raised my
daughter to be your daughter.
Now, take a picture of what your daughter is doing. What is that? What is that? What is this
WhatsApp TV?
What is this?
What is my daughter going to say?
Renu, my mother, uncle, don't tell me to behave like that with you. Let's go.
Uncle, don't make yourself look like the little lion Karthi.  What kind of cruel thing is it to tell someone to leave
the house
quickly, like in school, and then kiss them and
leave?   Is
that so?
What is this?
It tells you everything you did when you were in fifth grade
.
Oh my,
what is this?
This is my house anvil.  Your son is
like a temple.
What's the matter, it's a watery mess, don't let it go, don't let it go
.
Then your little one won't even go to the temple, but will
follow some girl and clean her up.  I fell in love with
that girl, not with any girl
.   If it's a
big deal, that's the final.  Come on, look
here, this love does
n't suit our family.
Doesn't it agree or doesn't wealth come from here
?  Banu,
he should be in this house, not
me.
I'll stay here,
tell him to go out.   Hey,
push me, what are you talking about?   The one who
came today is important, but you don't know if the people who came are the ones who went
.
You don't know this father who worked hard to raise you and educate you, who immediately took out the loan and gave you a shop loan
Hey, are you coming back?
All the gods of the universe pray for you not to be jealous
.  You are walking on a piece of dirt and rice, you are a fool  I have to
be there in five minutes.  Should I call you back?
Okay, sir.  I'm saying okay okay.
What's the problem, sir?   It won't start
.   Wo
n't start?   If the
car doesn't start when you come in front of our shop, it wo
n't spit out any of the people who drive it.  The
problem with my engine is ₹6000.
₹6000, or is it time to go somewhere else?
Why are you the owner of the Vadakambi Mooka shop? I'm
asking for 6000.
This guy is a good mechanic, he pays
3000 for the shop
. He has to pay 3000 for the shop rent.   It is
very difficult to get spare parts for the old 125C engine.  However, I will adjust it and
give it an orange color.  It is 9000.
What is it?
9000,000,
yes.
Alas, the time is changing, the meeting is going to be different.
Do you understand?   I have to
pay the balance to the tea shop.  The little
hand is driving another car.
Oh, leave it alone, sir, let's give it to him and
[ __ ] him, he's a good man.
The car started.
I forgot to turn the key on.  That's
a joke.
Oh, leave all that stuff behind.
You don't want it, I don't want it either.  4000
kututuru.   If there is
no problem with the car,
ask for 4000.
What a 3000 with Anuchir.  Hey,
the car started, it's
crazy.  It's like the three crazy people are saying, "
Hey, you're crazy, where are you?" "Hey, you're crazy,
you're crazy, I'll go and
pinch you."
I'm the one who came down and asked for ₹4000,
why are you asking for ₹3500?  He'll
put it in his pocket and bring it back.
Hey,
what time is it?  It was a mistake to marry a
local girl because we were listening to what they were saying
.  Why, what's wrong?  Hey, it's time to get up
early.
Here we come.   I
wish I was better.
We're running a medical shop, can
you ask me this?  Come closer, I
'm fine.   They
asked me if I looked good in this dress.   It's
torn.
Oh my, is it torn somewhere?   Do
n't worry, it's too hot.
Go get some glasses and come.
Okay.
What is this?
You asked for the class.
Why are you so black?
If it's glass, go get it, it's cooling glass
.
Okay, okay, why don't you go back to the right?
Okay, uncle.
[Music] They've
wasted their time telling this whole story of Kari Munja like it's an epic story.  Is it polite?   Starting
tomorrow, I'll have to put a grease stick on the stool
.
Hey, take a spanner.   There are only
three spanners in the store.  If
you ask me 10 11, where will I go? I'm on the phone.
Pick up the phone.
Sister,
hello,
brother, Muruga.
Tell me.
Saravana left home and went to court.
What happened? Oh my God. It
seems he's in love with some girl. It turned out to be a
big fight, your father knows about it
.  I left home for the coach
.   I see
.
I think you shouldn't touch something that's just above the skin.  There is no other way, I feel like I have to do it myself
.  Don't you
worry about anything?  Do you understand?
You thought, "Hey, sister, when did you
cut it?"
What house did you buy, Chaminna?
Why did you ask like this?
I have known this homeowner for ten years.  It's
enough if I say "I'm hungry".
He will give you the key with his eyes closed.   When
you close your eyes and drink, the key is in the safe,
you have to take it away.   There is
nothing wrong with kicking you out of your house.
Let's see if the dog comes.   It's been
400 years since a dog came, but only one has come.
Whose?
Father, I am the one who has come.
Samiya, I'm coming.   There's a
crack in the Love Matter house, and
the cable is leaking.   I have my
own clothing store, and
I'll come to the store.  Don't worry about anything.
You are the one who respects love, so don't
worry about love matters.
Giving your life for love.   I don't need all that
.  I ca
n't move because of your stupidity.  It's enough if you just go home
.
What's so wrong, Sami?   He
can't walk around without money in his hand.
How much is your advance?  How much is the fee?
Tell me that.
Advance ₹10,000, consumption ₹3,000,
separate ₹500 for water.
He is asking for ₹500 for water.
How does Sytis look after himself?
Sami, this seems very wrong.
Buy the key you want in advance.   Don't be shy
.
Kochana is going.
He's the owner of the house, so he won't get angry later.
What's wrong with you? Your
face is all withered.  What's wrong with
you?   A
deer without two arms shot a deer without four legs
.  It's not on that deer.  My
deer is on top.
What do you mean, two hands and four legs? He called
Naina and called her, but she cut him off
.
These girls are like this.
Okay, okay, you're not peeling, are you just putting two big ones in
?
The rates here are higher than in Pondicherry.   Okay,
okay.
[Music]
Throw all the dirty clothes into the sea and do
n't let anyone see this work. No one will see it.
[Music]
Now, what's the matter, the nose
piercing?   I'm making love to you, I'm
tired of feeding you, I'm coming
out and staying here, and
I'm also cleaning the ladies I see the other day.  That includes pregnant
ladies. Dad, this is the house
owner, Varadaraja.
Greetings, sir.  Are you okay?
Why did you come up with this idea?
Why is it doing such a harsh test
?  The dog has left behind a piece of cloth
.  You
thought your father was Mahadev.  Okay, look at this, it just kept going
.  Why am I talking so angrily to my father and mother?
Your mother has been crying since you arrived.  Please
come home respectfully.
You're going to be very spoiled if you stay here.   He's looking
good, like my little Yasa Arab
.  I've come,
who is it? Is it Dad? He's bored.
You're my man. Now call me and tell me I'll
make love to you.
Tell me, aunty, I
know.  The purpose of love is not set.
Our gardener will not agree.
You can put a breakup on someone who doesn't care about the breakup itself.
Hey old joke,
what else is a breakup?
This is a bigger deal than that.  What
girl are you coming to see tomorrow?  The
driver who saw the car.   Is
this all
normal, you ask?
You can only do this on his own terms
.
I'm watching all this, salt water, the matter.
What's wrong, Emma?
Will someone please come and take care of my daughter?
My brother, someone serious, came and picked up this bag and got it
.
Here are the details.  Just go and
see for yourself and tell me.
This guy is like a foreign cow
.  Machi told him to speak in English,
that's when China is there.
Hi, you saw the driver. I
know Divya.
Who knows Divya? We are family friends. I know.
15 years. We are going to get married soon.
Guys, let's
talk in Tamil
tomorrow. Anantharaman,
you are going to see Divya.
What's the point of this? We all
love each other.
Who is talking to you?
I love you, stay away.
I've seen a lot of this model.   Let's
go.
Hey,
you know, the two of them can't wait to learn the ropes?
What do you mean, everything we have is
over?  Is there any doubt?
I took a video to make sure it was something safe.  Show me that video. I want
to show you some of the videos we have.  You
go and see the girl tomorrow, make a promise, wrap the
talisman in gift paper, and then
stab her in the arm.
Look, the one who came here is the one who is going to make a profit. All
this is not a big deal, bro. Now, all this has
become very casual.  This is the time to cope by
saying that your own video doesn't count
.  Let's go.
Hey, Gambola, the face is wrong, the hand is wrong, it's like
that, peace bro,
my brother is a person, peace or not
[Music] I
said I would act well if I put my name on it, I'm a
stick figure, where is my mother, look,
come on, housewife, come, clean,
come, big place, recently, don't walk,
yes, this guy is very decent.   I'm just
like a beggar who is lying on the side of the road.
Who is Saravanam? Please call me, father. He
is giving Krishna a private room.
Did you notice that it is the puja room? Go, hello,
sir.  Hello, hello
Ukkaru
father, this is Saravanan.  The one who
saved your life, mother.  Oh, did this guy just break
his skull when he was hit by a driver he saw on Friends
?
What did you do?
Sami, I will come straight to the point.   The
whole town is talking about how you are such a good person that you will not be judged by this clan or caste.   With
that hope, I
come to ask for your daughter for my son.  Only two
people liked it.  Are we the ones who
make them big men and get them married?
Tell me what I'm saying. Everything
you say is correct, but our
customs are different.
We are the ones who are traditional. You are the ones who are not. What's the difference?
You go to the Kapaleeswarar temple.
We will go to the Karumari temple. We went to the
temple yesterday too.
[Music]
Hey, why don't you pick up the phone? You're the one who's going to kill me.
Look, I'm gone. Why are you calling me
so much?
Oh, where's the phone?  Wherever you are,
wherever you come from,
I will always be behind you.
Hey, Ola, come and get a drink right away
.  It
looks like a full mica.  Can knocking on the door
be empty?
Hey, leave him alone in this situation,
you say, "Wow, wow
Who has a problem
with a massage that is full of fun, a message like you're going to say something, aunty,
what's wrong with
Divya,
is it a match in the wedding ring before the wedding?
What did you say?
I just threatened you, I didn't scold you, I
told you what,  It's just a bit
scary to see what you're doing
.  Come on, come on.
What will I do to her now?
Why is this guy talking disrespectfully? It's a shame.
Aunty,
come here and say, "I just came to pray without her." Do
you know why she said that?
Show us your father is a bad person, I'll
drop everything and
come after you, okay?  Okay, if
she shows her father as a bad person, she
will come to you, sir, or to Sarip, madam,
or whatever. What do you
want? She goes and
says, "
Madam, why are you doing this?" Uncle, no,
he's not here, he's just like that. There are two
people in the stone. I'll just
take that away. Sir,
you're the one who gave me the shoe. Uncle,
what is her father like
? If so, can't you show him, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, be a bad person?
Hey, the whole town knows that you're a
good person.  She's going to go and
show me how bad I am, but
as long as your father is alive, you won't get her.   I told you, you told me, you told me, you
told me, I
told you, as long as that uncle is alive, he won't get that lady.
So what did Divya drink?
What's wrong with their father?   I think I
can make my dad a model because he does all the yoga.
Hey, what are you going to do, hey, don't drink and get drunk, don't get drunk,
mommy, you're in a bad mood, I have a
plan for tonight, just like that, I'll break it up with a
milkshake,
look.
Hello sir, is that so? I will come right away. Let me come right away.
Epp Saravana, the nurse is on her way to Kakusla. She is at the
hospital. I have
come from afar. I don't have any
knowledge.
Who is the nurse?
You
speak well. But you should talk on your phone.
That's my phone. Hey, I
thought you were the right horn. I
don't want you to be shaking like that. Look, you are beyond the
age you should live. You have
come to drink and drink. You have even drunk raw buffalo urine. Don't go and lie down. What am I going to do to make you
look ugly like this? What are you doing
now? Are you just
following me around to drink and drink
?
Yes,
you are all friends.
Friends are the ones who gather together the love of life.   I'm a drunkard, I'm a clingy person, I
don't have friends.  Hey, let's drive this way,
that way, the right way is the right way for work. I'm going to make a
mat for my uncle. I'm going to cut the end of the mat and
cut it. I'm going to make a mat for Divya and get
Diva
married. Oh, they're showing us something. Where is he from? [Music] Excuse me, you can admit him to the hospital. What's wrong with him? It's cruel. How can I tell you? You tell me. But he beat me and said, "What's wrong?" He called us and left
.   Wo
n't you tell me to keep listening?
It's a small alley, and it's
like a road.  I'll even give you that and give
you a
heart attack, sir.  He suddenly felt a chest pain and
fell down.  At
that moment,
our father, who was watching the whole thing with a smile, came and
rushed us to the hospital.   No matter what you do,
life goes on its way
.  It's not dawn, but a good soul,
heaven is what we have in our hands
.   You're
ugly, you're
not even good enough to say it, what kind of flow is he
saying? Sir, sir, sir, sir, what kind of flow is this? What kind of dialogue is this? Sir, sir
Come on, sir, there he is. Come on, look at him. He's
white,
like a tomato. Oh my God, don't you have eyes? What
happened, sir?
How are you?   I'll just tie it up and put it in my
mouth
.
Tell me, admit it yourself.
How are you?
Tell me, please.
Our admin can tell us a little better than us, sir
.  Claritia is available.  One
minute.  Sir, the blue shirt is here
.   Oh
my god, you just told me a flow,
can you leave it at that?  Thank you, thank you, God.  Thank
God.
It came and sir had a heart attack.  He
suddenly fell down, his heart pounding
.  Our brother had
rushed to the hospital at that time
.  But there is no blood on the way
.
Oh President, President,
President, you have left
us so unjustly. You have left
our sister an orphan. You
drunken boy, you drunken boy, I don't know what you are going to do now.
Brother, drag this man behind you and
pour a bucket of water on his head. Brother,
what are you talking about without being drunk? The
best
hand is the boost. The right net taste. If
you say so, listen to what
Ishwar,
the lion. What are you asking? You came to mourn in the house of death.
You are running away in fear.
What are you doing? You are drunk,
First, we can leave
here and go somewhere else
.
Can we go to the Thiruvarkadula Poonthu Pahaverkad?   I don't want
to eat fruit.
Let's go to Pondicherry.
Ask me, O dog, whether it is like a fruit orchard or Pondicherry.
Leave it alone, leave it alone, they're the ones who are talking about something without any knowledge and for
that reason, they're talking about it without any knowledge,
it's like somewhere unseen,
you can't trust them and send them out.
Please leave the door open.
Stay in my sight, booth.   What
Machan says is correct.  Only then will
we know what's happening here
.  If anyone knows about the three people who
put poison in their mouths, they will know everything.
That's what I'm saying. That's why I know.
Kulla Kamal went to
Jaishankar, Nagesh, Delhi, Ganesh, and
took revenge. Why did you
put poison in their mouths and kill them?
Why did our mother
tell the story to the mother brothers, who were trying to kill us? Are
you the only one who died?
I should have come in a hurry. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, let go, let go,
both of you are at fault. Don't fight in the death
house. Leave the money. Leave the
money. Hurry up. Who are you? Who are you?
Instead of asking everyone else, go and
ask who he is. Oh,
he's a terrible person. Be
careful. He'll
tell you
where you're going.  Let's go and ask and
come back. I'll
wait somewhere for you to come and get it.   Turn on
the camera.
Mr., who was a great social worker and humanitarian, served as the Tahsildar.   It is with
great sadness that we announce that Anantharaman passed away this morning due to a heart attack
.
Currently, not only
his relatives,
but also numerous members of the public, government
officials, and political leaders are coming to pay their last respects
.
He fell down, heartbroken.
Fortunately, at that moment, four younger brothers
came and took him to the hospital,
but he died on the way.   One should
not be leprous or leprous in the morning.  You should not measure yourself with a stick.
You should remain calm until you have a moderate amount of leprosy.  Do you understand?
Then no one will have any doubts.   I
have doubts.
Alas, the correct love knot has come, like a cat coming when it's time to become a fish
.  The bag didn't get stuck in the water
.
I'm starting to suspect that our uncle is dead.  The
child
fortune teller said he would live until the age of 90.  Now he died suddenly
.  What does that
mean?
It means the fortune teller is lying.
Whenever
I find out who is the reason for this, I will
stab her in the gut with one punch and
leave with a garland.   To
which temple?   I will
go wherever I want.   Let
's beat the sandal.  Hey
Mandi Bhai Mandi Bhai Mandi Bhai Aruna,
this is the only way to drink this waste, you talk so much, drink
that bottle, drink that bottle, drink that, drink
this, this is the time of begging  If you
give this to the sea, you will go, oh
Stop the prank, Saru
Meeraju. The
hard disk is not working.
The video is not coming.
Knowing that he would tell me if it was a real waste, I
took the hard disk and lit it on fire
.
It can't be. Tell me what he's
saying.  Just say it.
Is Adis burning?
What are you saying?
Hey, rice, rice.
There is no pearl in a rotten body.
Look, he understands your words.  They won't respect my intellectual
Seruppala as a
gangster.
This person needs to be a good person.
This
should be taken with a good label, without being criticized.
[Music]
[Applause]
Brother, am I the only one talking about CCTV Chidambaram
?
Okay, okay,
sir, he's talking so rudely.
Brother, you were talking nicely before,
what happened now?   If
the fear is gone,
do you know what the commissioner will do with this matter, just a coffee to the collector?
Leprosy is a disease that is spread by your own hands.
Hey, what are you doing,
are you giving me a little milk?
Hey, give me coffee or milk, but I'm
asking you what's wrong with not telling me a story.  Can you give me money
?  Is it impossible?   No way
.
Why is that?   Did
you give my number to anyone who doesn't look like you?
Who did you give it to?
Hey Chidambaram, now I'll show you who I am
.
Brother, I'm the one who wrote
that CCTV with Chidambaram
.   Have
I got the money ready?  Tell your brother to just
reduce the amount a little
.
He's not even one person.  This brother doesn't have
anything to say about him
.  I will make a profit of 1000-2000 rupees for you
.  But you can help me
.
Tell me, what should I do?
He sent me a video of the
murder, did
you send that video to this
number?
Why not?
The video we had was
deleted.  It's only up to you
.  That's why.
Oh
okay, please send it.  Thanda Soru
Dies
Hello,
Thanda Soru, you are a wise dog,
you have told me one thing worth ₹ lakh,
my dear, I am very angry, you have been
congratulating me since I was a child, what do you
say, why don't you say something,
because now that is the only one who has come on the sign line,
you do one thing, you scold me, remember all that,
then scold me,
Sarana, oh oh oh oh, what did
Abdul Kalam say, what did he do,
this Abdul Kalam said, what did he do,
our father, where is
he, full tit, you don't worry about anything,
he is safe, a watchman will
come and hide your bank next to you,
somewhere, which watchman is
Iyer in the state.
But when my son went to his daughter's house, he
told me that this marriage would only happen if I died, and he kept feeding me and nursing me
.
I am a scoundrel.  I saw what happened
I asked Yasar if he had told me to show him four animals, saying, "Hey, hey  He said, "No, I'll watch it
."  Who?
Who?
My child,
my child, who has killed me,
burned me like a firecracker on the road and torn the case.   Will what
he said happen?
What's up, Iyer, is the line clear? If
anyone
calls me a big brother,
they will go all the way to the Salt Fort.
That's my big brother's specialty.
[Music] There's no one to
blame for that. The
policeman said, "
Why am I going to dance Satansa?" "
Who is Saravana?" "
I'm the one," he said. "
How come he
came down with a chest pain?" "We
picked him up and went to the hospital." "We lost our way,"
he said.   The one who
was lying at our house,
sir, just go straight, sir, and then turn right,
sir   I'm not crying now, to
tell you the truth, I'm really going to cry
.  Don't buy it.
Hey, no matter what
question that person asks you over and over again, you have to
answer the same way
.  I saw the movie Papanaasa, you guys, where did you leave it?
You shouldn't have opened your mouth.
[Applause]
Sister, call me and put on your
jacket.
[Music]
Janu Janu Siya,
your son is calling you. Look,
why is this? Azish, papa, papa,
like Azish,
Azish, father,
what is happening in the world? Aunty, it's
time, daddy, Azish, it's time for Papa, it's time for
your son to call you.
Look,
someone told you to go and get some anesthesia.
This is a big deal.  Okay, let's wait and see if we can get another
good day.
First, you're not going to die, okay? First, no matter
what you do, they don't even know how to die, they just sit
there crying and crying, not even knowing how to breathe.
What do they do?
Let them go. Do you know the story about how some people came to
life when they were buried in a cemetery
?
Still joking, can we talk about
something? Why are you so stupid?
What did you leave behind like this?
What did you leave behind?
What is this story?
Oh oh oh uncle,
oh uncle, you have come, uncle,
who are you?
[Applause]
Uncle, you have built a house and
built it for the planetary entry. Look, uncle, look, uncle, look, I am the only one who
will say that this area is beautiful. Uncle, you have
collected all the property and left. Uncle, look,
uncle,
look, uncle, thank you, I
said I will go with you and put the nightcap together.
Uncle, you are the only one who has gone. Oh,
look, look,
uncle,
what is that man doing? We are
beating our lions in the single bedroom.  The boss came to the
triple bedroom, said you're living in a tip top, and he
said he'll buy you all the work at the garage,
that's all he said. He
even said he'd tie the girl up
.  Yes,
no, who asked you to go to Varandi? I didn't want to
go.
What did you say? Will you give it to the girl who was not alive?
[Music]
Hey, what are you doing? Are you running away after picking up the fruit?
How does the money you gave to your uncle work?
He's a crazy guy, he
can't hold anything for 10 minutes, he's just eating panipuri in his sleep, his
mouth is still open
.   If
you ask me, we are really going to die now.
Delhi is over.
Someone please make me some coffee.
Saroja
[Music]
Shreya, what did you do? Okay, okay, okay, my
body is broken